So, I typically try to not go too
specific into the identity, politics,
culture stuff because it's a bunch of
slot [ __ ] for low IQ people that are
stuck in the past and that are dying out
rapidly. But people keep asking me about
this whole Amanda Seals interview. It's
two white-kinned women who are
pretending to be Amastads.
But the thing is this, these women
nowadays are just it's the it's it's not
just these women. It's the entire black
community.
They put themselves in a really bad
position as far as society goes. They've
kind of boxed themselves into a corner
and now they're more so on an island
alone.
But in their twisted minds, they assumed
that Asians and Latinos and all these
other miscellaneous groups in the United
States were going to join them in their
fake gay war against white people. But
if that's the case, then we would have
to look at things from the eyes of a
black person. I don't know if any of you
have ever met anyone black, but
everything is binary. It's either black
or white. To be white is to be married.
To be white is to have kids. To be white
is to be gainfully employed and to love
God. To be black is the opposite. To not
have family, to not have kids, to not
love religion, to think everything is
racist, to be angry and alone. So when
you ask us which one would we choose,
we're going to choose white. So for them
is, oh my god, they want to be white.
It's not that. We just don't want to be
black. Black is evil. See, we're people
with culture. We're not lost. We have a
language. We have an ethnicity. We have
a nationality. The black Americans, they
call themselves a color. They're not
even Americans.
They will they will die saying how
they're not Americans, but they can't
even get out of the country and get a
passport that says I'm black from Black
Landia. They're confused. So what
Amanda, people don't understand this
about Amanda Seals. She's gay.
What these gay people thought was that
they can organize the blacks and the
gays and they were going to start this
revolution.
Nobody wants to be gay with you. You're
going to have to be gay and trans and
twisted and mentally ill on your own.
They're looking at Latinos and they're
saying, "Okay, these people are becoming
more conservative and Christian by the
hour. We are having families. We are
getting married." The blacks are going
in a complete different direction, but
for some odd reason, they thought we
were going to be with them. I don't know
where they got that twisted idea from,
but someone lied to them. So, you see
them lashing out. To be black is to be
gay. To be trans is to be black. I've
never heard anyone black say that that's
not true. So, it is true.
Latinos and no other group in this
country is doing that [ __ ] You guys
are going to kill yourselves on your
own. To be gay is depopulating your own
society. You You won't have You can't
have kids if you're gay. It's over. To
be trans means you self sterilize.
You're mentally ill and you're confused
about your gender, gender dysphoria. You
will never have kids. You will never get
married. You will never have a family.
That's why those kids are just going
crazy shooting people. They have no
future anyway. And the blacks are trying
to encourage us to do what they're doing
because nobody wants to die alone.
Baby, we are Americans now. We're
Hispanics. We're Latinos, but we are
Americans. We're not blacks. Blacks are
not Americans. We are. You guys have
citizenship because you were born here,
but you'll never be Americans. You don't
have a love for the country. You have
zero patriotism. You've been spoiled by
welfare and social services. So, you're
afraid to leave this country. At any
given time, any of these blacks that
hate America could have moved to South
Africa. They could have learned to speak
Zulu or Kasa or another black language.
No one's forcing you to speak English,
which is a white language from England.
It's a choice. But they're upset because
now they're turning out to just be gay
all by themselves. People are becoming
less and less gay and less and less
black. So they're becoming lonier and
lonelier. Take a listen. This is how
confused these people are. This is only
I'm going to play two videos for you.
>> Hey, you know that's some I don't know.
Homophobia is weird to me.
>> To me, too. Because I feel like in
essence, but this is the big thing.
>> Why do we have time for this?
>> But this is the big thing. I always
looked at it like, and I would say this
all the time because I really didn't
understand it. Like, how can a black
person be homophobic when
>> two white-kinned women speaking as if
they are just dark as night? This this
is the mental two white-kinned women can
look in the mirror and say the word
black. That means that they can easily
lie to themselves, lie to others, and
they cannot be trusted. If these two
white-kinned women can look in the
mirror and they see the color black,
they're mentally ill. Don't forget that.
>> It's in essence the same thing. Somebody
hating you for something that you can't
control. But the big issue is is that
there's a big amount of black people,
old, young, and in between that feel
like that it's a choice. And that's
where it's it goes.
>> But even if it was a choice, so what? Be
because if my point isn't the same. So,
if my point is, how can you as a black
person, right, and we know about our
history here, we know about being
discriminated against, people hate us
for no other reason. Well,
let's not take it that far.
You're 13% of the population. Well, you
were 13% of the population. As of today,
you are 9% of the population thanks to
Epstein's research and the vaccine.
Next fact,
people hate you because with your with
your minority population, you're more
than 60% of all the violent crime. Also,
there is a culture of not snitching,
which means a lot of people who should
be in prison for violent crime are
exonerated because nobody will show up
to testify against them. There's not one
race of humans in the United States, in
our republic, cuz remember, we're not a
democracy cuz black people keep saying
democracy. That's another thing people
hate about black people. We're not a
democracy. We are a constitutional
republic. There's not one group of of
any humans in our republic that enjoy or
want to live around black people. Why is
that?
High amounts of violence, high amounts
of theft ease and will lie to you in
your face. The thing is this. We've all
had a shared bad experience with black
culture. Now, there are individual good
black people, but as a whole, we've all
shared bad experiences with them to the
point where we would rather work 100
hours a week than be poor enough where
we have to live next door to black
people. We all get up every single Let
me tell you, do you know how cheap it is
to live in the hood?
Why is it that cheap? Because who lives
in the hood? So, it's it's it's pros and
cons. We all would love to pay $600 a
month for rent in Los Angeles.
We would all opt out to do it, but it
comes with a there's one catch. You got
to live next door to black people.
Nobody is willing to risk their own
lives and the lives of their children
for $600 rent. So, the further away from
the black people that you live, the
higher your rent will go up.
Isn't that a [ __ ] shame that that's
the calculation that determines rental
values in America?
That doesn't mean that there's a problem
with everybody else in America. That
just means there's a really big problem
with black people. See, you don't have a
race problem in the United States. You
just have a problem race. And it's
unpopular opinion. And it's uh it's not
something that people want to talk about
because they're worried about being
cancelled, worried about being um you
know, somebody want to get online and
talk about, oh, you look ugly or or
this. Nobody gives a [ __ ] about your
opinion. You guys are gay.
We we nobody cares about what black
people say anymore. Why do you think
they played that guy yelling out the um
n-word with Tourette's, but they cut out
the other parts of the show they didn't
like, but they left that part in? They
could have re-recorded it. No one
respects them anymore. They don't have
kids. They're gay.
They complain about everything that mean
and then they're sick from the vaccine.
They're dropping like flies.
We're not going to have to deal with the
problem race in 20 years because of
Epstein's research and Bill Gates and
Camala Harris making sure they all took
it.
Amanda Seal sitting here saying, "Well,
I don't know why people don't like black
people." What the [ __ ] is wrong with
you? Are you insane? The question is,
what is there to like that you can dunk?
Well, that's what the [ __ ] is so good
about that? There's nothing that she can
say to make you think that she has any
brain cells left. She's completely
confused and detached from reality. But
let's listen to these two white-kinned
women continue to banter on about
[ __ ] and I will correct them
>> then being How can you hate a gay person
when it's the exact same thing? They're
[ __ ] gay. They have no choice in it.
But there's a group of people that feel
like they do have a choice in it.
>> Even if they did have a choice, why do
you care?
>> Oh,
why do we care?
Well, let's see here. First things
first, every [ __ ] gay person is now
representing in all of our children's
cartoons right now. It went from, well,
we want to just get married to each
other and stay to ourselves and live in
our own communities to, well, I want to
dress up as a woman and read um read
stories to your kindergartener. Also, I
want to be able to tell your
kindergartener that they should keep
secrets from you, and I want to become
your your kid's teacher in first grade.
I want to put up a gay pride flag, which
is a terrorist flag. I want to put it up
in our classroom with a BLM flag. And I
want to convince your kids that they're
oppressed and they're less than, so that
they would join my fake revolution.
Also, it'll turn them against your
parents. That way when these teachers
molest them, there won't be any
accountability because they won't be af
they will be too afraid to tell because
they won't want to tell because they'll
lose the only thing they have left.
Remember, they get you to ostracize your
parents so that the school and the gay
community becomes your family. And if
you're molested by them, you'll lose
both of your families. So then the kids
really have nowhere to go. That's why
they turn them against you. That is the
policy. I don't want to. Every time I
turn on a good movie that I want to
watch, magically at the end there's some
gay sex scene with two [ __ ] men. It's
unnecessary.
It's all about conditioning people to
let down your guards and accept the fact
that there are people who want to
sexualize your child and you're a
homophobe if you don't accept it and
you're a bigot and you're a racist if
you don't want these people to molest
your kids and groom them. That's the
side that Amanda Seals is on. That's the
only part that we don't care about. If
gays lived in their own community, like
people from Mongolia or some other
ethnic group and they just had their own
stores and their own shops and they left
our kids alone, nobody would give a
damn. The problem is they don't even
want to get married to each other. They
just want kids. They want access to
kids. That's it. There's literally a
group called Gays Against Groomers
because there's such a monster problem
with grooming in the gay community that
there needed to be a group that came out
and said, "Hey, they're not us. We're
not like them. We're actually different
and there is a problem. We we knew there
was a problem, but they're just
confirming it. We're not even we're not
making this up or exaggerating. They
target kids. Trans people target kids.
Gay people target kids. If they stayed
to themselves and up to their own
devices, nobody would give a [ __ ] that
they exist. I don't know what you do
with your dick at night. You can stick
it in a blender for all I [ __ ] care.
My issue with you is that you want to
bother kids. You're recruiting from
pools of kids. You want to be in schools
so you can have access to freshminded
um kids who are impressionable at a
young age. and parents because this
didn't happen to us as kids. We're
oblivious to the fact that it's
happening to our kids right now and it's
state sanctioned.
The teachers are the principles are
covering up for the teachers. The
teachers are covering up for the
counselors and they're all targeting
your sons, especially if they're white.
The black kids, they're they just hand
them over. But it's the white kids that
have parents that are a lot harder to
get. That's why these teacher hate these
white kids so much.
It's not hurting you. Like [ __ ] have
choices all day long that n like
literally like cisgendered heterosexual
people make choices all day long that
hurt other black people.
>> I'm sis.
>> Yeah. She's uh she's so gay that it
hurts. But she's alone. Women were not
meant to be Amanda Sills's age with no
kids, no husband, no responsibility,
no purpose. They were not meant to be
that age. But listen what she thinks
about us Latinos because we don't want
to be gay with her and she was wrong and
now she can't come back from where she
is. Take a listen.
>> Because you know how many Latinos are
out HERE LIKE GO TRUMP, GO TRUMP. WHO
like want this dictatorship? You know
how many Latinos don't give a about
black people because they want to be
white so bad that they have assigned
themselves to that whiteness. Give me a
conversation about I wish you cared
about your life so bad so much. somebody
I follow who is of Latin descent said,
"I wish you guys value your lives a
little more."
>> And that's the number one thing that us
Latinos, the reason why even if we live
close to blacks, our kids don't play
with them. We don't associate with them.
We speak Spanish because we don't want
to speak English and these people think
that we can talk to each other. We're
not your friends. We're not your allies.
We do enjoy the 600 rent, but we're
fighters. Other races of people are are
a little bit more timid, not as
aggressive, and they don't have the
size. Latinos, we are big, we can fight,
and we're not afraid of black people
like Asians and other groups are. So, we
don't mind moving into the hood because
their strength in numbers, and we have
our own gangs as well. So, that's why we
can deal with them, but we're already
pushing them out of Compton, of Lynwood.
We're pushing them out of all these
different areas that we've taken over in
Los Angeles and around the country
because they don't value families. They
don't have families. They don't believe
in families. To believe in family and to
have kids and to get married and take
care of your family is what blacks tell
you is the are the hallmarks of white
supremacy. So to be white is to love
your family and to have a family and
want to be married. To be black is the
opposite. We don't want to be black. If
that's what it means to be white is by
taking care of our family and having
kids, then we're white. If that's what
if that what works in your small binary
mind of confusion of gayness, then
that's fine with us. Somebody calling us
white is not an insult. It's a
compliment. Because when you got to
think, well, what is the opposite of
white? It's black. In which universe is
someone calling you black a compliment?
That's the worst insult that you can
call somebody because that means you're
calling them gay. Nobody wants to be gay
with you guys. You guys are gay on your
own. And why do you think soon as a
black person gets married, they say he's
not black anymore? As soon as he gets a
job and starts making money, he's no
longer black. Soon as he wants to have
kids, well, he can't have kids with a
black woman because the black woman is
naturally a victim of everything. So
your kids are going to be victims.
People want their kids to be Americans,
not victims. You're not a victim in
America. There's only there's only one
group of people that still share that
delusion. And that group is dying out so
fast. Amanda Seals is withering away.
She's past the age of being able to have
kids. She will never replace herself.
Her mental illness and her ideology dies
with her. Her vagina is no more good.
Nobody wants her. She's a permanent
victim. She's not even wor She's not
even not even good enough for sex. She's
that's she's cooked. It's over. But you
can still hear people bring her online
because there's still a handful of black
people that love to feel like victims.
Why do you think the v why do you think
this Gavin Newsome situation resonated
with so many black people where they
liked it so much? Let's take a listen.
Actually,
it's this video. Let's watch this one.
>> I'm not, you know, I'm not trying to
impress you. I'm just trying to impress
upon you. I'm like you. I'm no better
than you. You know, he's talking like a
robot because
the black mind is feeble. It is the
equivalent of a fouryear-old in groups.
Some as individuals can understand the
people that you can talk to that are
black that are not heavily autistic,
they'll tell you that he sounds crazy.
But when we step back and look at the
community as a whole, I can understand
why he's speaking to them in a fourth
grade level and why he says to them,
"I'm just like you. I'm an idiot. I
scored a 960 on the SATs." Do you know
you just spelling your name correct, you
get like a 870 or something, that means
you are stupid as [ __ ] And there's no
excuse for that if you are grown up and
raised in America. But it depends on how
you lived here. Were you raised American
or were you raised to be black? If you
were raised to be black, then being dumb
is being cool. And if you try to teach a
black kid something or work on them with
their grades, well, that's considered
racist. Which is why they got rid of all
the standards in schools so that these
kids who cannot read, spell, or add are
still passed up through grades and
graduated with a third grade level for
basic understandings of any curriculums,
which is bad. The rest of us are held to
a higher standard. the black kids
because these schools don't want to seem
racist. The district doesn't want to
seem racist. They are still graduated.
And then an H.B.CU will bring in these
kids who are reading at a third and
fourth grade level and then will have
the nerve to give them a diploma and
tell them you guys achieved something
because they can't hold you back either.
Or the H.B.CU will be accused of being
racist. Then when you try to get hired
in the workforce and you don't fit the
culture and you're not good at your job
and you get fired, well, now the
company's racist. The the whole thing is
a dead and archaic and dying system.
This whole pipeline of treating blacks
special. It's not. It doesn't work. And
it killed them off. They told you you
were super special. That's why you had
to take the vaccine first. You guys were
cooked anyway.
It's over. So now we have to move on.
But this is the reason why Gavin Newsome
felt so comfortable saying this is
because of idiots like [ __ ] Amanda
Seals.
>> I'm a 960 SAT guy.
And you know, and I'm not trying to
offend anyone, you know, trying to act
all there if you got 940.
But he's a [ __ ] liar. Gavin Newsome
scored no less than a 1220 on his SATs.
He is a [ __ ] liar.
He's a liar.
but he understands his audience
now. He's wasting his time. They're not
going to be the ones making up a
majority of his voters anymore. There
have been millions that have died since
2021 in California specifically. His
base is really just the illegals and the
gays. And he is at this convention
working on the black gays. It's not and
they're in Atlanta. So, this is about
his presidential This is not him being
reelected. This is about his
presidential run. This is a waste. But
he says, "I'm just like you, a 960 SAT,
and a mayor of Atlanta, who I'm sure
scored far above that, is laughing at
the audience. But maybe they are too
dumb to realize that they're being
basically made fun of. If you're so dumb
that you think this is funny, you don't
realize they're insulting you, then that
means that what Gavin Newsome is saying
about them is correct. That's why I
don't feel any type of way when I talk.
I'm not just saying this to say it. I'm
I've literally I explain everything in
detail and I show the evidence. And if
somebody has a counterargument, let's
have the conversation. But it's hard to
have a complex conversation with someone
when they're autistic. They're not they
they just get angry and get frustrated.
And I mean, they don't want to fight,
but they they do get if they could, they
would, which is that's how we got to
where we are now.
>> Literally a 960 SAT guy. I cannot you
you've never seen me read a speech
because I cannot read a speech.
>> Oh my [ __ ] So he's basically saying I
mean what do black people pride
themselves on? Not being able to read
only being able to count money.
Um not having and and being gay. And
that's the only thing that and and and
being trans. There's nothing else that
people are saying that they're so proud
of when it comes. That's it. That's the
whole culture. So when you go back to
someone like uh Amanda Seals, she's just
mad that we don't want to be gay with
them
>> because you know how many Latinos are
out here like go Trump, go Trump, who
like want this dictatorship. You know
how many Latinos don't give a about
black people because they want to be
white so bad that they have assigned
themselves to that whiteness. Give me a
conversation about I wish
>> we it's not our job. We are adults. It's
not our jobs to give a [ __ ] about
anybody but ourselves. We have our own
families to worry about. [ __ ] you and
your family. You are on your own. You're
black. Go take care of your black family
or lack thereof and go sit in a corner.
You're on a gay island where you're
fighting an imaginary war against white
people that you already lost. If you
really were serious about your hate and
anger for white people, you would have
left this white country and you would
have stopped speaking a white language.
You're literally living under white
people where they're the majority. You
could have renounced your citizenship
and you can learn to speak [ __ ]
Swahili. Why are you still engulfing
yourself in white culture?
You're a grifter, but you grifted
yourself into a corner and then you
found out that nobody wants to jump off
the bridge with you. You jumped on your
own. She threw away her best child
rearing years and marriage years. She
threw them away fighting in a fake
revolution that nobody else even paid
attention to that never came to
fruition. No one was about to start
attacking white people to show
themselves solidarity to you. Are you
insane there? You have nothing to offer
but pain and lies and and [ __ ]
insults and just trauma from nothing.
you. The only thing you can offer is
mental illness and you're mad that
everybody else is not sharing in your
mental delusion. And she's frustrated as
hell. Look at her.
>> You cared about your lives so bad. So
much. Somebody I follow who is of Latin
descent said, "I wish you guys value
your lives a little more."
So her response to somebody like myself,
and this is what I always say, I said,
"I would spend more time with black
people if they valued their lives a
little bit more." Her response to when
we all say that, everybody of every race
says that about black people, that their
whole world would be different if they
just valued their lives more. And her
response was, "Shut the [ __ ] up."
And there here in lies the problem.
We don't want to live next to you. We
don't want our kids around you. We have
very good reason because you guys are
dangerous and you don't value life. You
don't have families. You have nothing to
lose. We have everything to lose. We're
Americans. We're going to be moving
forward here in this country. We have a
country to save from you. The good thing
is the vaccine has already saved the
country from you. Now we can move on to
bigger and bad better threats like China
and birthright citizenship and anchor
babies and the the push from the World
Economic Forum to invade the United
States with the third world from these
Islamic countries. The black threat is
neutralized thanks to the vaccine and
Jeffrey Epstein. Now we have other
things to worry about. But periodically
I will point these things out because
these videos, my videos are not always
played instantly. People play them weeks
from now and they share them. And this
is information that people are going to
say, I've actually figured this out.
I've been thinking the same thing, but
no one else wanted to talk about it. I'm
not necessarily worried about winning
popularity contests with everybody. I'm
a man. No one likes men. No one likes
us. So, I'm not used to that anyway. I
don't need everybody to praise me and
tell me I'm right. I already know I am.
This is through life experience. And I
love my black friends. But my black
friends are not these [ __ ] psycho
gays like Amanda Seals that are don't
understand why people don't want to be
around them. Even my black friends don't
want to live around black people. I
wonder why that is. Soon as people get
money, they don't want to get away from
black people. Explain that and then show
me how that's white supremacy. It's
because Oh yeah, because once you get
money, now you're no longer black. You
get it? Now they call you white. To be
black is to be poor, too. To be black is
to be gay. To be black is to be mentally
ill and trans. To be black is to be
poor. To be black is to be desolute. To
be black is to have no country, no
nationality, no religion.
I have all of those things. Not confused
at all. Let me know what you think. If
you agree or disagree, like, subscribe,
share the video. I'll be back on with
another topic in about 20 minutes.
Remember, it's America first and America
only.
>> I've been needing to find a new
apartment, which has not been easy with
credit as bad as mine. Luckily, I found
co-signing.com. They connected me with a
co-signer who helped me get my dream
apartment for me and my dog. I just paid
a small fee and was able to move in
fast. Get the co-signer you need for the
apartment you want. Check out
cosigny.com